JORGE ANGEL PAEZ

Software Developer | JavaScript & Python Instructor

Buenos Aires, Argentina +54 2932 540493 | jorgeangelpaez@gmail.com Portfolio | LinkedIn

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Information Technology professional with extensive experience in different roles and tools. In recent years, I have focused my development in the Front End Development area, complementing my independent professional activity with teaching JavaScript and Python. I combine technical skills with management and administration experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JavaScript & Python Instructor | EducacionIT, Buenos Aires 2022 - Present

- Development and delivery of educational programs in JavaScript and Python
- Supporting students throughout their learning process

JavaScript Tutor | Coderhouse, Buenos Aires 2022 - 2023

- Tutoring and support for students in JavaScript courses
- Review and feedback on practical projects

Front End Developer | Freelance

2019 - Present

- Design and development of user interfaces
- Implementation of web solutions with React and JavaScript

Head of Communications and IT | Argentine Navy

2004 - Present

- Management of communications and IT systems
- Supervision of technical teams

Unix and Linux Systems Administrator | School of Marine Sciences, Buenos Aires 2012 - 2013

Server administration and maintenance

Technical incident resolution

Managing Partner - Front End Developer | Acrux D+D, Trelew 2009 - 2013

- Co-management of the development company
- Design and implementation of web interfaces

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science | Universidad Empresarial Siglo XXI, Córdoba

2023 - Present (In progress)

Master of Business Administration (MBA) | International Institute of Global Studies for Human Development, Málaga, Spain 2018 - 2019

Specialist in Telecommunications Systems | National Defense University (UNDEF), Puerto Belgrano 2010 - 2011

Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration | National Defense University (UNDEF), La Plata 2004 - 2008

Electronics Technician | National School of Technical Education 1, Punta Alta 2001 - 2003

CERTIFICATIONS

Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate (SFPC) | CertiProf 2022

SCF - Scrum Certified Fundamentals | SCRUM Study 2022

Installation, repair and maintenance of Vision Master FT Radar & ECDIS | Northrop Grumman Sperry Marine Support Center, New Orleans, USA 2018

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Front End Development: React, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, SASS, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap
- Back End Development: Django, Python, Java , Spring, NodeJS

• **Project Management**: Agile Methodologies, Scrum

Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
BaaS: Firebase, Supabase

• Systems: Unix/Linux Administration

LANGUAGES

• Spanish: Native • English: Advanced

• Portuguese: Intermediate

• French: Basic